<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Informs customers of Soundpath&apos;s new look and logo</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Rebrand Customer Communication</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing Our New Look: What It Means For You</subject>
    <textOnly>Soundpath Legael New look



Dear {!Contact.FirstName},

Recently we debuted an updated style and logo that represents the next chapter for the Soundpath brand. We are thrilled with our new look, but even more excited about what it represents: our commitment to evolving Soundpath so we can continue bringing you the most reliable and intuitive web, audio and video meeting solutions possible.

You are probably wondering why we decided to rebrand Soundpath. Here&apos;s why:

• Not everyone knows that in 2008 Soundpath joined the PGi family. We wanted a style and logo that better associates us with PGi as well as our parent company&apos;s reputation for innovation in the online meeting marketplace.

• Soundpath exists with one, simple goal in mind - to best serve the specific needs of law firms. Therefore, we&apos;ve tweaked our name from Soundpath to Soundpath Legal to show our devotion to and expertise in the legal industry.

During our transition, which will occur gradually over the next 3-6 months, your current service will NOT be disrupted; you will, however, start to see our new Soundpath Legal brand come to life in our communications to you and in the products and services we deliver.

As always, we appreciate your business and look forward to serving you in the future.

Regards,

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Phone}

P.S. Going to ILTA? Swing by Booth #212 to see our new look in person or schedule an onsite product demo here!

© 2013 PGi 3280 Peachtree Road, N.E., Suite 1000 Atlanta, GA 30305 USA © Premiere Global Services, Ltd.  |  PGi All rights reserved. If you prefer not to receive emails from PGi, you may unsubscribe.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
