<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>This is for following up post show.</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>PGi_Standard</letterhead>
    <name>Gartner Symposium 2013 Follow Up</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Nice to Meet You at Gartner Symposium 2013</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName},

Thank you for your interest in PGi at Gartner Symposium/ITxpo Orlando.

PGi has been a global leader in collaboration and virtual meetings for over 20 years. PGi&apos;s cloud-based solutions deliver multi-point, real-time virtual collaboration using video, voice, mobile, web streaming and file sharing technologies. PGi solutions are available via desktops, tablets and mobile devices, helping businesses worldwide be more productive, mobile and environmentally responsible. PGi has a global presence in 25 countries and an established base of over 40,000 enterprise customers, including 75% of the Fortune 100™. In the last five years, PGi has hosted nearly one billion people from 137 countries in over 200 million virtual meetings. For more information, visit PGi at www.pgi.com.

Why PGi?

SAFE AND SECURE – Security is critical. Whether you&apos;re a large enterprise or a small business, PGi meeting products give you world-class security that you can depend on.

EASY TO USE – PGi products are designed to make virtual collaboration as easy as possible. This will help increase adoption and usage across your organization. At the same time, minimizing the time your IT staff has to spend troubleshooting employee issues with your meeting software.

ANYWHERE ACCESS – As companies move to more remote workers and flexible work options, it&apos;s critical that IT can enable employees to work anywhere at anytime. PGi products work just as well on mobile devices so employees can host or join a meeting in the office or on-the-go.

Get to know our products at http://www.pgi.com/about-pgi-products. I would be happy to schedule a demo at your request.

Best,

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}
{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}














If you no longer wish to receive these emails, please unsubscribe.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
</EmailTemplate>
