<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>PGi_Standard</letterhead>
    <name>TAG Social Savvy Invite</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Join LinkedIn &amp; PGi at the TAG Social Savvy Awards</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName},

Please join me on November 5th  at the TAG Social Savvy Awards Event in Atlanta. PGi is a premier sponsor of this signature event along with LinkedIn, Junior Achievement of Georgia and the Technology Association of Georgia (TAG)

“Social” is an exciting and evolving space that many companies are still learning about and experimenting with so we will be recognizing thought leaders and innovators in this space on November 5th at the 2013 TAG Social Savvy Awards from 4-7pmET.

The Keynote Speaker is Luke Davies from LinkedIn. Blake Canterbury, CEO &amp; Founder of Beremedy will also give a special presentation. Awards will be presented to winners from UPS, Intellinet, Cbeyond, Manhattan Associates, SunTrust and Rural Sourcing. The awards presentation will be led by our emcee, Conn Jackson, Atlanta TV &amp; Radio host.

A &quot;genius bar&quot; powered by students from SPSU and PGi will be available to answer all your questions about social and mobile apps. The awards presentation will be followed by breakout sessions with the winners and guest speakers. This is your chance to ask questions and learn from the experts in an intimate setting.

To top it all off the venue is phenomenal. It is at the brand new JA Discovery Center at the World Congress Center. We will be having our special event there in the later afternoon but during the day this center is a place where students from all over Georgia are able to interact within a simulated macro-economy, and take on the role of employee, tax payer and consumer. Within the JA Discovery Center there is JA BizTown where students receive unique job as­signments and work in teams at their assigned business. By the end of the simulation each student completes a day’s work, develops a personal budget, deposits a paycheck at the bank and makes purchasing decisions. There is also the JA Finance Park which gives students the rare opportunity to experience their personal financial futures first-hand. Upon entering the center, students receive a ‘life situation’ with job, income, education, and family scenarios. Based on their adult persona, students visit businesses in the simulation to gather information to make financial decisions, such as managing a household budget, using banking services, and making purchasing and investment decisions. You have to see this place!

So all in all this will be a fun, informational, educational and valuable event for you to attend and I really hope you can make it.

For more info and to register, visit: bit.ly/TAGSocialSSA13

Thank you,
{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}









If you no longer wish to receive these emails, please unsubscribe.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
</EmailTemplate>
