<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Email introducing you as the Account Manager (EN, FR)</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>I am your AM</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>{!Contact.FirstName},{!IF(ISPICKVAL(Contact.LeadSource, &quot;Social Media&quot;),&quot; FRENCH&quot;,IF(ISPICKVAL(Contact.LeadSource, &quot;Web Chat&quot;), &quot; German&quot;,&quot; are you enjoying your PGi conferencing solution?&quot;))}</subject>
    <textOnly>{!IF(Contact.MailingCountry=&quot;France&quot;,&quot;Bonjour &quot;, 		IF(Contact.MailingCountry=&quot;Germany&quot;,&quot;German &quot;,&quot;Dear &quot;))}  {!Contact.FirstName},

{!IF (Contact.MailingCountry=&quot;France&quot;,&quot;

Je suis votre gestionnaire de compte PGi, je vous contacte pour m&apos;assurer que vous profitez pleinement de notre solution de conférence, mais aussi pour vous garantir mon aide conernant n&apos;importe quelle requête que vous pourriez avoir.

Cette année, PGi vous contactera régulièrement pour vous garder informé des différentes mise à jour de votre produit. Ces messages ont simplement pour but de vous renseigner sur les nouvelles options, vous assurant de tirer le meilleur de votre solution de conférence.

J&apos;aimerais avoir une brève discussion avec vous, pour revoir votre compte et vous faire part de l&apos;évolution de l&apos;espace de conférence PGi. Je vous appellerais dans les jours qui viennent pour organiser cette discussion.

J&apos;espère avoir l&apos;opportunité de vous parler très bientôt.

Cordialement,

&quot;,  IF(Contact.MailingCountry=&quot;Germany&quot;, &quot;German text&quot;,  &quot;

As your Account Manager at PGi, I want to reach out to ensure that you are enjoying your conferencing product and to assure you that I am here to help you with any queries you may have.

This year PGi will be communicating with you regularly to keep you informed of updates to your product. These messages are simply to let you know about new features, thus ensuring you get the most from your conferencing solution.

I would love to have a quick chat with you soon to review your account and to tell you about some exciting developments in the PGi conferencing space. I will give you a call over the next few days to organise.

I hope we have the opportunity to catch up very soon.

Kind regards,

&quot; ))}

{!Contact.OwnerFullName}
{!Contact.OwnerTitle}
Tel: {!Contact.OwnerPhone}
{!Contact.OwnerEmail}

24/7 Customer Support / Re-send Account Details:
UK Free Phone: 0800 279 9748 | UK: +44 207 026 5970 | Ireland: +353 (0)23 883 2493 | France: +33 171 230528 | Germany: +49 697 1044 5443
Email: eureservations@pgi.com</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
