<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Prospecting email to marketing with presentation ebook content</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Marketing- Download Presentation Ebook</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Get your next presentation in lights- Free eBook</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName},

Do you often find that your creativity is being stifled by the day to day mundane tasks of organising events, company town hall meetings, product launches and large corporate meetings?

You only have one chance to make a first impression with your audience. Benefit from PGi’s vast event experience…

Download their new ebook- “The Little Black Book of Presentation Ideas” and benefit from the following:

7 tips for creating capturing presentations
7 great ways to incorporate new tech, tools and toys to wow your audience
7 mind-blowing techniques to give your presentation the IT factor and stand out from the crowd

Download your Little Black Book of Presentation Ideas and change your presentations with simple tricks.

Great presentations are important, but it is vital that you can show your masterpiece in all its glory. Please contact me today to arrange a quick meeting to discuss how we can assist you in acheieving your collaboartive advantage.

Be creative and let us handle the rest,

{!User.FirstName}

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}

Head of Amazing and Creative Virtual Meetings, PGi

{!User.Phone}

{!User.Email}


ABOUT PGi

At PGi, we like to say that we give people and the companies they work for a “Collaborative Advantage”.  Because we know that better collaboration leads to better results.

For over 20 years, PGi has given people the tools to meet, collaborate and innovate.  We design our tools to make collaboration easier. For us, it’s not only about the technology. It’s about the people using the technology.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
