<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Template provided by Forrester.</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Forrester CIO Forum Invite</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Forrester&apos;s Forum For CIO, EA, Infrastructure &amp; Ops, Security and Risk, And Sourcing Professionals</subject>
    <textOnly>Forrester&apos;s Forum For CIO, EA, Infrastructure &amp; Ops, Security and Risk, And Sourcing Professionals

Forrester&apos;s Forum For CIO, EA, Infrastructure &amp; Ops, Security and Risk, And Sourcing Professionals Architecting Tomorrow&apos;s Business Outcomes
May 6–7, 2013 • Washington Marriott Wardman Park • Washington, DC

PGi is pleased to announce its participation at Forrester&apos;s Forum For CIO, EA, Infrastructure &amp; Ops, Security &amp; Risk, And Sourcing Professionals — and you&apos;re invited!

The drumbeat of business change is speeding up. Digital technology — social, mobile, analytics, cloud, and devices — disrupts business models and value streams, introduces new competitive threats, and comes with new demands from your customers and employees. The technology, competencies, and skills you put in place today will embody your digital business future.

Forrester&apos;s Forum For CIO, EA, Infrastructure &amp; Ops, Security &amp; Risk, And Sourcing Professionals will address tomorrow&apos;s digital-fueled business challenges with dedicated programs for the   following decision-makers:

For CIOs: Understand the demands that tomorrow&apos;s digital-fueled business outcomes   place on leadership, competencies, and ecosystems.

For Enterprise Architecture Professionals: Paint tomorrow&apos;s vision, integrate with   your business, and define the new solution architectures required to   deliver tomorrow&apos;s business outcomes.

For Infrastructure &amp; Operations Professionals: Deliver the   agility and flexibility needed to ensure the business outcomes of the   digital age.

For Security &amp; Risk Professionals: Rethink security and run at digital   threats and risks to secure tomorrow&apos;s business outcomes.

For Sourcing &amp; Vendor Management Professionals: Redefine partner ecosystems and strategies to fuel tomorrow&apos;s business outcomes.

Be sure to register with our promo code for reduced pricing. We look forward to seeing you in Washington, DC!


EVENT DETAILS

Date
May 6–7, 2013
» view agenda

Location
Washington, DC


Save $405* when registering online with PGi&apos;s promo code: BT13SP

Contact Us
+1 888.343.6786
+1 617.613.5905
events@forrester.com

CONNECT WITH FORRESTER: COMMUNITIES · BLOGS ·  ·  ·  ·

*Discount applies to new, online registrations at the non-client, non-Early Bird rate. Cannot be combined with other offers.

© 2013, Forrester Research, Inc. Forrester is a trademark of Forrester Research, Inc.
Forrester Research, Inc. · 60 Acorn Park Drive · Cambridge, MA 02140
Tel: +1 617.613.6000 · Fax: +1 617.613.5000

If you prefer not to receive emails from PGi, you may unsubscribe: http://experts.pgi.com/email-opt-out</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
