<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Gartner PCC 14: Email Invite 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>See you at Gartner PCC?</subject>
    <textOnly>Gartner Portals, Content &amp; Collaboration Summit 2014

Join PGi at Gartner Portals, Content &amp; Collaboration Summit 2014 in Los Angeles, CA.

Thinking about attending the upcoming Gartner Portals, Content &amp; Collaboration Summit 2014, May 5-7, in Los Angeles, CA?

Deliver Excellent Engagement Through Mobile, Social and Analytics
How well you engage with employees, customers, partners, suppliers and constituents is the most important determinant of business success. But developing that prowess requires the right tools and technologies to be in place. And in today’s world that means embracing Mobile, Social, and Analytics.

Attend Gartner Portals, Content &amp; Collaboration Summit and see how to deliver excellent user engagement by leveraging these new tools, technologies and trends to the fullest.

We look forward to seeing you in May!


Gartner Portals, Content &amp; Collaboration Summit 2014
May 5 – 7, Los Angeles, CA



Register Now With Priority Code PCC144

Receive  $300 off the standard price:
Visit gartner.com/us/pcc or call 1 866 405 2511


Sponsor of Gartner Portals, Content &amp; Collaboration Summit 2014


Special offer

Register with priority code PCC144 to save $300 on the standard price.

Web: gartner.com/us/pcc

Email: us.registration@gartner.com

Phone: 1 866 405 2511

© 2014 Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates. All rights reserved. Gartner is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. or its affiliates. For more information, email info@gartner.com or visit gartner.com. Gartner, Inc., 56 Top Gallant Road, PO Box 10212, Stamford, CT 06904-2212.

Update your profile: If your interests have changed recently, you may want to update your details so that we can continue to provide you with the information most relevant to you. gartnerinfo.com/eventsinsider

Unsubscribe

&lt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
