<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>PGi_Standard</letterhead>
    <name>Business Development Intro Letter</name>
    <style>formalLetter</style>
    <subject>Is your state-of-the-art company using &quot;old school&quot; conferencing?</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName}:

· Do you invite guests to conference calls using cut and paste to include the numbers?

· Do you and your guests have to dial a passcode to join a call?

· When you are on a mobile phone and you need to join a meeting do you have to dial a toll free number and then a passcode?

· When you are on your iPad do you have to go find a phone to join a call or find a computer to join a web conference?

· When you are on a conference call and realize you need to share a document do you have to send out a new invitation - hang up and rejoin a new meeting on the web?

· Do guests to your web meetings have to download an application to join?

· Do you have to wait for a face to face meeting to actually see your business partners?

Our customers don&apos;t have to do any of these things!

My name is Susan Porter and I work for Premiere Global (PGi). We have been providing audio conferencing for more than 20 years to 75% of the Fortune 100 and we recognize that the convergence of audio conferencing and web collaboration is the next generation of communication.

We have two new cloud based services that make standard audio conferencing a thing of the past. These web tools by themselves cost less than a nice lunch out...but since PGi is also an audio conferencing company - unlike other web tools ours also come with audio.

You probably already have some form of collaboration tools – but do they represent your company image? Can they be branded? Do they help you keep costs down by allowing you to get to know your business partners personally without having to travel to them? Ours can.

I know your time is valuable – so is mine. Don’t take my word for it; please respond to this email with a convenient time and date and I will set up a half hour online web meeting to show you what our tools can do to help you be more successful!

Best wishes,</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
</EmailTemplate>
