<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Covers Philippines, Mobility and Web 9/6/2012</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>PGi_Standard</letterhead>
    <name>Chevron Update Letter for Users</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>News you can use...from PGi (your audio conferencing provider)</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName}:


My name is Susan Porter and I am your account manager from Premiere Global (PGi). We provide Chevron audio conferencing services.  Below are some items I thought might be useful to you.

1.  International Coverage - We now offer service in the Philippines – it is an 800 number that anyone in the Philippines can use to join your calls. To use it, you must have an account with a higher level of security. If you need to upgrade your account, just let me know and we will take care of it. There is no cost difference for the higher security account, but it is required for local calling in six APAC countries.

2.  Mobility Tools - If you have an iPhone, Blackberry or iPad there is a great new way to access your conference calls. You can download an app and can join your call without entering the dial in number or passcode! Really. Just get the free app here: www.globalmeet.com/tools. Download the one you need. Take a quick look at the user guide (also on the site). It is more than 20 pages but it is all pictures so it takes about 5 minutes to run through.

3. Data Sharing - If you need desktop data sharing we are now offering that to Chevron as well. GlobalMeet for web is $34 a month (12 month minimum) for now and will drop in price as more Chevron employees use it. The web tool also includes a video option. More importantly, it does not require a download for your guests…and it gives you your own URL so your address stays the same and you can even store presentations and files on the site. Think of it as your room in the cloud. Just contact me and I will get GlobalMeet for web added to your account.  Here is a link to a 1:16 minute video that shows what it looks like and how it works:  GlobalMeet Video.

Let me know if you have any questions. I am happy to give you a quick demo of any of our services. At PGi, we want you to have perfect, productive meetings!


Best wishes,

Susan Porter

Account Executive


Office: 408-448-7959

Mobile: 650-996-2315

iMeet® room: iMeet.com/SusanPorter


Going to Dreamforce 2012? Visit us in Booth 138 and Meeting Room A5, Hall E!


&lt;?xml:namespace prefix = v ns = &quot;urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml&quot; /&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
</EmailTemplate>
