<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Send to all your current prospects and customers to invite them to this event</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>EMEA:UK: SAE May Webinar</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>How to Gain the Collaborative Edge</subject>
    <textOnly>PGi, the Meetings Experts


Complexity Enemy at the IT Gate:
How to Make Sense of the  Collaboration Clutter
Business Breakthrough Leadership Series


{!Lead.FirstName},

How would you describe your current collaboration strategy?

Perhaps you have old legacy solutions still in place but are hoping to invest in new robust solutions for the future. Sometimes understanding the right route to take can prove challenging.

Well this webinar will address these points and offer up an engaging discussion leveraging the expertise and past experiences of our expert speakers.

Register now for this Webinar on May 20th where our expert panelists will help you:

How to make sense of the multitude of options available to enterprise organisations when developing a robust solution for collaboration as part of a wider UC strategy
Consider the implications of legacy solutions still in place when building for the future
Build sustainable and flexible solutions ready for deployment and fit for the future

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}

{!User.Phone}


Who should attend:   This seminar is ideal for B2B business leaders who want to learn more about how to leverage the right collaborative solution to acheive sustainable competitive advantage
When:   Monday, May 20th
Time:   2:00PM BST
9:00AM EDT

Eric Masseboeuf, Head of International Voice Business Unit Orange Business Services
Phil Goldby, Managing Director, EMEA of Sherpa Digital Media
William A. Haskins, Senior Analyst &amp; Partner Wainhouse Research

AWARDS &amp;
ACCOLADES

2012 Silver Edison Award Best New Product, iMeet

2012 Silver Stevie Award Most Innovative Tech Company of the Year

2011 Stevie Award People&apos;s Choice, iMeet

InformationWeek Top 250 Innovators of the Year

© Premiere Global Services, Inc. and/or its affiliates
PGi 17 Godliman Street, London, EC4V 5BD, UK</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
