<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>PGi_Standard</letterhead>
    <name>Executive Intro</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Unified Communications</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName}:


By way of introduction, my name is Susan Porter. I am an Account Manager at PGi.  PGi is an innovator and leader in the Collaboration/Unified Communications space, hosting nearly 23 million people in over 5 million virtual meetings every month. We understand the challenges that global enterprises like {!Company__c.Name} face and would like to have a conversation with you and the appropriate team that evaluates audio, web and desktop video conferencing technologies to have a better understanding of your landscape and specifically, your challenges. &lt;?xml:namespace prefix = o ns = &quot;urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office&quot; /&gt;


The business of PGi is driving down the excessive costs of audio, video, and web-based communications, while improving top-line revenue, enhancing customer satisfaction and making your meetings the most efficient part of your day.


Many of our customers are industry leaders and are highly visible in the market.  The business outcomes we deliver are cost savings, business process efficiencies and an improved working environment through better meetings.  Some of our unique differentiators include: a singular focus on collaboration; an obsession with the end user experience; and  simple, effective collaboration solutions. In addition to our proprietary products, we also integrate and partner with best of breed vendors such as Microsoft, Adobe and WebEx.


We can quickly determine our relevance and ability to assist your company based on our initial conversation. I will follow up in the next few days for a meeting.  Otherwise, please direct me to the correct contact regarding our request.


Thank you very much and we look forward to meeting with you soon.


Best wishes,




Susan


Susan Porter

Account Executive, PGi

408-448-7959

Susan.Porter@pgi.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
</EmailTemplate>
