<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>PGi_Standard</letterhead>
    <name>3 Reasons for Sales</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Meeting Request:  Re: Making Quotas in a Digital World</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName}:


I realize your time is important, so I thought it best if I shared just three reasons why having a meeting would be valuable at this time:

1. Audio conferencing and web collaboration are converging.

If your sales teams are using tools from a few years ago - it is a good time to reconsider.  As the third largest audio conferencing provider in the world, PGi has a history of innovation and an unparrallelled VOIP based global platform.  We took this platform and added web collaboration tools.  The result is clear calls, an impressive list of international access points and easy web tools that are already integrated with our audio tools.


Why pay for a web service separately from your audio conferencing when it is less expensive to simply pay for one and get both?  Why have separate dial in numbers when you can have just one and not even have to dial in?


2. Reducing costs does not mean you have to reduce service.

Customers are switching from services like Webex and Skype because with PGi they learn that they can have security, avoid downloads and make it easy for prospects and customers to attend demos and discussions.  And reduce costs and get better service in the process.


You might already be using a web collaboration tool.  It might even be free.  But is it secure?  Does it require a download for attendees?  Is it easy to use?


3. PGi is chosen by 75% of the Fortune 100 for our innovation.

Our solutions give you a URL that doesn&apos;t change.  Think of it as your &quot;room&quot; on the web.  You can store sales presentations on it.  Print it on business cards.  Lock it or leave it open.  Why is that useful for sales?  If an account executive is on a call with a customer and that suddenly needs to share a document - they don&apos;t have to hang up, schedule a meeting and then dial back in - the AE simply asks the customer to step into their virtual room by typing an easy URL - their name.  Then, the AE can share their desktop.  It is so easy it makes us wonder why we never it did it that way before!


There is more to share, but as I said in the subject - I would like to have a meeting.  Let me help you understand the new options for selling in the digital world.


I am based in San Jose and would be happy to stop by {!Account.Name} in person.  Or, if now is not a good time, I am happy to check in with you later.  Please let me know when would be convenient.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
</EmailTemplate>
