<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Invite your HR/benefits contacts to hear Karrie Andes speak about benefits enrollment</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Boring Benefits? Webinar Invite</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>[Webinar] Rejuvenate your Benefits Enrollment</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName}, You spent hours developing a fabulous benefits package, only to find out a mere third of your workforce read through the material. How are you going to improve your benefits engagement?  Attend this HR.com + PGi webinar,  Boring Benefits? Rejuvenate the way you Communicate!,  to learn about a variety of benefits communication techniques designed to increase benefits engagement for your workforce. You&apos;ll get:

• Inspired ideas for new hire orientations

• Guidance on how to conduct virtual health and benefit fairs

• Creative social media tips for open enrollment

You&apos;ll also hear how PGi has more than doubled participation in our HDHP consumerism plan.
Register now, it&apos;s free!  

Boring Benefits? 
Rejuvenate the way you Communicate! 
March 6, 2014 11am Eastern Time Click here to register!

Sincerely,
{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}

P.S.  If you are not the correct person to speak to about collaboration solutions for benefits enrollment within your organization, it would be great if you would direct me to the correct individual. Thanks in advance for your help!

AWARDS &amp;
ACCOLADES

Best New Product – iMeet 2012 Silver Edison Award
People’s Choice – iMeet 2011 Stevie Award
Most Innovative Tech Company of the Year 2012 Silver Stevie Award
Top 250 Innovators of the Year InformationWeek

‘iMeet has succeeded where many others have failed.’ ZDNet
‘A wonderful convergence of usability, responsiveness and connectivity.’ TechRepublic

© 2013 PGi  3280 Peachtree Road, N.E., Suite 1000 Atlanta, GA 30305 USA
© Premiere Global Services, Ltd.  |  PGi All rights reserved.

If you prefer not to receive emails from PGi sales representatives, you may unsubscribe.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
