<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Forrester-provided email template</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Forrester&apos;s Forum (CIO) 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Hope to see you at Forrester&apos;s Forum For Technology Management Leaders</subject>
    <textOnly>Forrester&apos;s Forum For Sales Enablement Professionals

Forrester&apos;s Forum For Technology Management Leaders Unleash Your Digital Business
May 5–6, 2014 • JW Marriott Orlando Grande Lakes

PGi is pleased to announce its participation at Forrester&apos;s Forum For Technology Management Leaders — and you&apos;re invited!

Register online with our special promo code TM14S to save $405* off the regular Forum rate.

As digital technology sweeps us all into the Age of the Customer, enterprise technology professionals must step into a new leadership position — not just capably deploying solutions and platforms. You&apos;ve heard it before, but now it&apos;s for real: Today&apos;s technology leaders must be leaders of business and creators of future enterprise value.

With track sessions designed to fit your particular job role and needs, this Forum will be your best opportunity to reinvent your business technology organization, differentiate you from your competitors, and prepare you to unleash your digital business.

Forrester&apos;s Forum For Technology Management Leaders will teach you how to turn emerging technologies and processes into quick-win, high-impact digital capabilities, and you&apos;ll walk away with:

A first look at Forrester&apos;s not-yet-released book: &quot;The Mobile Mind Shift: Engineer Your Business to Win in the Mobile Moment&quot; by Ted Schadler, Josh Bernoff, and Julie A. Ask, Forrester Research.

Training and tools to redefine your products, services, and sourcing strategies.

The opportunity to meet 1-On-1 with your favorite Forrester analysts and hear Forrester CEO, George F. Colony, deliver the opening remarks.

Be sure to register with our promo code for reduced pricing. We look forward to seeing you in Orlando!


EVENT DETAILS

Date
May 5–6, 2014
» view agenda

Location
Orlando, Fla.

Booth Number
PGi #207


Save $405* when registering online with PGi&apos;s promo code: TM14S

Contact Forrester
+1 888.343.6786
+1 617.613.5905
events@forrester.com

CONNECT WITH FORRESTER: COMMUNITIES · BLOGS ·  ·  ·  ·

*Discount applies to new, online registrations at the non-client, non-Early Bird rate. Cannot be combined with other offers.

© 2014, Forrester Research, Inc. Forrester is a trademark of Forrester Research, Inc.
Forrester Research, Inc. · 60 Acorn Park Drive · Cambridge, MA 02140
Tel: +1 617.613.6000 · Fax: +1 617.613.5000</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
