<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Invite pre-show</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Gartner SYMPOSIUM ITxpo 2013</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>See you at the Gartner SYMPOSIUM ITxpo</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName}, Please join PGi at this year’s  Gartner SYMPOSIUM ITxpo in Orlando, Florida, October 6-10, 2013 as we discuss groundbreaking new communication and collaboration trends for enterprise organizations. We will be hosting on-site demos of our software, iMeet and GlobalMeet in Booth 1038. Come find out how PGi is helping organizations get more business done by addressing the challenges around collaboration. In working with over 40,000 customers worldwide and 75% of the Fortune 100™,  PGi has found 3 key challenges common to enterprise organizations:

• iPads, tablets and smartphones integrating into existing technology platforms (BYOD)

• High cost and low usage of video telepresence rooms versus the ease of use of HD video conferencing tools

• Fragmented approach of current audio, web and video conferencing solutions

PGi enables companies to consolidate their entire organization&apos;s audio, web and video conferencing needs making it easier to meet anywhere, anytime and on virtually any device. This means more enjoyable meetings for more engaged employees.
I&apos;d like the opportunity to show you how PGi&apos;s award-winning collaboration solutions can meet your needs at the Gartner SYMPOSIUM ITxpo. Please contact me to set up a personalized demo.
Hope to see you there!
{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}P.S.  If you have a colleague that would be interested in learning more about PGi&apos;s collaboration solutions, please feel free to pass along this information to them. Thanks in advance for your help!

AWARDS &amp;
ACCOLADES

Best New Product – iMeet 2012 Silver Edison Award
People’s Choice – iMeet 2011 Stevie Award
Most Innovative Tech Company of the Year 2012 Silver Stevie Award
Top 250 Innovators of the Year InformationWeek

‘iMeet has succeeded where many others have failed.’ ZDNet
‘A wonderful convergence of usability, responsiveness and connectivity.’ TechRepublic

© 2013 PGi  3280 Peachtree Road, N.E., Suite 1000 Atlanta, GA 30305 USA
© Premiere Global Services, Ltd.  |  PGi All rights reserved.

If you prefer not to receive emails from PGi sales representatives, you may  unsubscribe.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
