<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Use this as a first contact with a SUSPECT with an HR title</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Suspects: HR, 1st Contact</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Do your job candidates expect video?</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName}, 

If you&apos;ve thought about incorporating video into your talent acquisition efforts, this whitepaper is for you.  Click here to read, Why Online Video is Changing the Candidate Engagement Model: http://cdn1.hubspot.com/hub/147341/file-18645767.pdf

In a recent HR.com webinar, Kevin Wheeler explained how video can be used throughout the recruiting process, from the initial candidate assessment to onboarding new employees. He even went so far to say Video is the most significant thing to happen to recruitment in the next 2 to 3 years.  

In addition to the benefits with the recruiting process, in working with over 40,000 customers worldwide and 75% of the Fortune 100™,  PGi has found that HR professionals need easy to use, cost-efficient collaboration tools to:

-Recruit the best employees
-Onboard new hires remotely
-Train and communicate more effectively
-Manage large-scale open enrollment and benefits communications
-Manage change
-Increase employee engagement

I&apos;d like the opportunity to share with you how PGi&apos;s award-winning collaboration solutions are designed to enable HR departments, and even an entire organization – to meet anywhere, anytime and on virtually any device. Please let me know your availability for a 15-minute virtual meeting by contacting me at the information below; otherwise I will follow up with you next week.

Sincerely,

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}
{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}

P.S.  If you are not the correct person to speak to about collaboration solutions within your organization, it would be great if you would direct me to the correct individual. Thanks in advance for your help!

AWARDS &amp; ACCOLADES

Best New Product – iMeet 2012 Silver Edison Award
People’s Choice – iMeet 2011 Stevie Award
Most Innovative Tech Company of the Year 2012 Silver Stevie Award
Top 250 Innovators of the Year InformationWeek

‘iMeet has succeeded where many others have failed.’ ZDNet
‘A wonderful convergence of usability, responsiveness and connectivity.’ TechRepublic

© 2013 PGi  3280 Peachtree Road, N.E., Suite 1000 Atlanta, GA 30305 USA
© Premiere Global Services, Ltd.  |  PGi All rights reserved.

If you prefer not to receive emails from PGi sales representatives, you may  unsubscribe: http://experts.pgi.com/email-opt-out</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
