<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>IT Buyer&apos;s Guide to Web Conferencing</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>How to choose the best web conferencing tool</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName}, 

Cloud-based solutions, collaboration tools, web meetings – all important topics relevant to the day-to-day life of businesspeople today. With the growing importance of virtual collaboration, how will you choose the tool that will support your team? Would a &apos;how to&apos; guide to choosing the best solution help you get started?  Click here to download:  The IT Buyer&apos;s Guide to Web Conferencing. http://cdn2.hubspot.net/hub/147341/file-64935924-pdf/docs/ITBuyersGuidetoWebConferencing.pdf

Use our handy buyer&apos;s guide to:

• Check for key features in a web conferencing tool

• Ask the right questions before buying a new web conferencing solution

• Find the tool that supports how your company meets

PGi enables companies to consolidate their entire organization&apos;s audio, web and video conferencing needs making it easier to meet anywhere, anytime and on virtually any device.

I&apos;d like the opportunity to share with you how PGi&apos;s award-winning collaboration solutions can meet your needs. Please let me know your availability for a 15-minute virtual meeting by contacting me at the information below; otherwise I will follow up with you next week.

Sincerely,

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}
{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}

P.S.  If you are not the correct person to speak to about collaboration solutions within your organization, it would be great if you would direct me to the correct individual. Thanks in advance for your help!

AWARDS &amp;
ACCOLADES

Best New Product – iMeet 2012 Silver Edison Award
People’s Choice – iMeet 2011 Stevie Award
Most Innovative Tech Company of the Year 2012 Silver Stevie Award
Top 250 Innovators of the Year InformationWeek

‘iMeet has succeeded where many others have failed.’ ZDNet
‘A wonderful convergence of usability, responsiveness and connectivity.’ TechRepublic

© 2013 PGi  3280 Peachtree Road, N.E., Suite 1000 Atlanta, GA 30305 USA
© Premiere Global Services, Ltd.  |  PGi All rights reserved.

If you prefer not to receive emails from PGi sales representatives, you may  unsubscribe. http://experts.pgi.com/email-opt-out</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
