<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>PGi Security Report</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>How secure are your web meetings?</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName}, 

Ever wondered how a technology company approaches security? With over 40,000 enterprise customers, including 75% of the Fortune 100™, we are committed to protecting the privacy and business continuity of every client we serve.  Click here to download the report:  Learn How PGi Addresses Security, Resilience and Business Continuity. http://cdn2.hubspot.net/hub/147341/file-63353175-pdf/docs/PGiSecurityReport.pdf

Read this report and learn about PGi&apos;s business practices for:

• Dedicated security and business continuity protocols

• Secure physical environments and infrastructure

• Data security, resilience and redundancies with ongoing risk assessments

PGi enables companies to consolidate their entire organization&apos;s audio, web and video conferencing needs making it easier to meet anywhere, anytime and on virtually any device.

I&apos;d like the opportunity to share with you how PGi&apos;s award-winning collaboration solutions can meet your needs. Please let me know your availability for a 15-minute virtual meeting by contacting me at the information below; otherwise I will follow up with you next week.

Sincerely,

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}
{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}

P.S.  If you are not the correct person to speak to about collaboration solutions within your organization, it would be great if you would direct me to the correct individual. Thanks in advance for your help!

AWARDS &amp;
ACCOLADES

Best New Product – iMeet 2012 Silver Edison Award
People’s Choice – iMeet 2011 Stevie Award
Most Innovative Tech Company of the Year 2012 Silver Stevie Award
Top 250 Innovators of the Year InformationWeek

‘iMeet has succeeded where many others have failed.’ ZDNet
‘A wonderful convergence of usability, responsiveness and connectivity.’ TechRepublic

© 2013 PGi  3280 Peachtree Road, N.E., Suite 1000 Atlanta, GA 30305 USA
© Premiere Global Services, Ltd.  |  PGi All rights reserved.

If you prefer not to receive emails from PGi sales representatives, you may  unsubscribe. http://experts.pgi.com/email-opt-out</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
