<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Use this as a first contact with a SUSPECT with a Sales title</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Suspects: Sales, 1st Contact</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>How to use video in the sales cycle</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName}, 

If you’ve ever thought about how to set your sales message apart from the competition’s, this research brief from Aberdeen Group is for you.  Click here to see the impact video can have on your sales cycle:  Video and Collaboration: Fighting the Forgetting Curve: http://cdn2.hubspot.net/hub/147341/file-20888802-pdf/docs/0473-rb-videoforsales-tk-05.pdf

Aberdeen states that Best-in-Class companies are more than twice as likely as all others to use video in the closing stage of the funnel (33% vs. 12%) and 57% more likely to use video at the sales qualifying stage (47% vs. 30%). In working with over 40,000 customers worldwide and 75% of the Fortune 100™,  PGi has found that sales professionals need easy to use, cost-efficient collaboration tools to:

-Hold face-to-face meetings with prospective clients virtually
-Increase daily appointments by reducing travel time
-Read non-verbal cues that can have a tremendous impact on how your message is being received
-Show and talk through your products, solutions or proposals
-Host or join a meeting remotely on any device

Here is how it works –  watch this video, using iMeet for Sales: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FWPdgvUjSeI

I&apos;d like the opportunity to share with you how PGi&apos;s award-winning collaboration solutions PGi&apos;s award-winning collaboration solutions are designed to enable sales departments, and even your entire organization – to meet anywhere, anytime and on virtually any device. Please let me know your availability for a 15-minute virtual meeting by contacting me at the information below; otherwise I will follow up with you next week.

Sincerely,
{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}
{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}

P.S.  If you are not the correct person to speak to about collaboration solutions within your organization, it would be great if you would direct me to the correct individual. Thanks in advance for your help!

AWARDS &amp; ACCOLADES

Best New Product – iMeet 2012 Silver Edison Award
People’s Choice – iMeet 2011 Stevie Award
Most Innovative Tech Company of the Year 2012 Silver Stevie Award
Top 250 Innovators of the Year InformationWeek

‘iMeet has succeeded where many others have failed.’ ZDNet
‘A wonderful convergence of usability, responsiveness and connectivity.’ TechRepublic

© 2013 PGi  3280 Peachtree Road, N.E., Suite 1000 Atlanta, GA 30305 USA
© Premiere Global Services, Ltd.  |  PGi All rights reserved.

If you prefer not to receive emails from PGi sales representatives, you may  unsubscribe: http://experts.pgi.com/email-opt-out</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
