<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Use this as a second contact with a SUSPECT with an IT title</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Suspects: IT 2nd Contact</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Follow-up - collaboration solutions</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName}, 

In case you missed it, according to a  recent Forrester Study, 72% of tablet users report that meeting access – either getting everyone into a meeting or participating in a meeting away from a desktop or laptop – is the main stumbling block to using web conferencing at their companies.

As one of PGi’s meetings &amp; collaborations experts, I am keenly aware of the collaboration challenges faced by enterprise organizations.  PGi has over 40,000 customers worldwide and 75% of the Fortune 100™,  We offer a suite of collaboration solutions to support your unique video, web or audio needs - making it easier to meet anyone, anywhere, anytime, on virtually any device. For more information on our collaboration solutions check out the video links below:

-iMeet – virtual face-to-face meetings anytime, anywhere in HD – intuitive collaboration tools, no guest downloads or special hardware required. http://youtu.be/KmffxYSY-7w

Watch this video on using iMeet on your iPad: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LboRgZnk8kY

Watch this video on using iMeet on your iPhone: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4NgdC0Xbmc

-GlobalMeet – delivers easy to use audio-only or web-conferencing options for you to present to colleagues across the organization or anywhere around the globe. http://youtu.be/Qb2qAela5zA

Our collaboration solutions are unique to experience and very easy to use – but you have to see it to believe it. Please let me know your availability for a 15 minute virtual meeting.

During our virtual meeting, I will show you how PGi helps organizations improve their communication and collaboration. Please feel free to contact me at the information below. Otherwise, I will follow up with you shortly to be sure you received this email.

Sincerely,

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}
{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}

P.S.  If you are not the correct person to speak to about collaboration solutions within your organization, it would be great if you would direct me to the correct individual. Thanks in advance for your help!

AWARDS &amp; ACCOLADES

Best New Product – iMeet 2012 Silver Edison Award
People’s Choice – iMeet 2011 Stevie Award
Most Innovative Tech Company of the Year 2012 Silver Stevie Award
Top 250 Innovators of the Year InformationWeek

‘iMeet has succeeded where many others have failed.’ ZDNet
‘A wonderful convergence of usability, responsiveness and connectivity.’ TechRepublic

© 2013 PGi  3280 Peachtree Road, N.E., Suite 1000 Atlanta, GA 30305 USA
© Premiere Global Services, Ltd.  |  PGi All rights reserved.

If you prefer not to receive emails from PGi sales representatives, you may  unsubscribe: http://experts.pgi.com/email-opt-out</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
