<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Invite your HR/recruiting contacts to hear Kim Pettibone speak about recruiting tech</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Virtual Handshake Webinar Invite</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>[Webinar] The Virtual Handshake</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName}, 

Technology may be intimidating to the HR professional who has spent years learning the ropes to deliver quality candidates that meet a variety of requirements. But whether you are new to your role or a seasoned professional,  attend this HR.com + PGi webinar, The Virtual Handshake: How to Combine the Latest Technology with Classic Recruiting Principles,  for best practices and real-life advice on:

• How to open doors to connect with great candidates that are hard to reach

• Tips and lessons learned from one-on-one virtual interviews

• How to “flip the funnel” with candidates

Register now, it&apos;s free!  The Virtual Handshake: How to Combine the Latest Technology with Classic Recruiting Principles March 19, 2014 1pm Eastern Time 
Click here to register: http://www.hr.com/stories/1390847684933

Sincerely,
{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}
{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}

P.S.  If you are not the correct person to speak to about recruiting tools for talent acquisition within your organization, it would be great if you would direct me to the correct individual. Thanks in advance for your help!

AWARDS &amp;
ACCOLADES

Best New Product – iMeet 2012 Silver Edison Award
People’s Choice – iMeet 2011 Stevie Award
Most Innovative Tech Company of the Year 2012 Silver Stevie Award
Top 250 Innovators of the Year InformationWeek

‘iMeet has succeeded where many others have failed.’ ZDNet
‘A wonderful convergence of usability, responsiveness and connectivity.’ TechRepublic

© 2013 PGi  3280 Peachtree Road, N.E., Suite 1000 Atlanta, GA 30305 USA
© Premiere Global Services, Ltd.  |  PGi All rights reserved.

If you prefer not to receive emails from PGi sales representatives, you may  unsubscribe: http://experts.pgi.com/email-opt-out</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
