<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>LOB- GM Audio</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>EMEA Sales- GM Audio</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Take sales productivity to a new level</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName},

I wanted to introduce myself as a PGi Collaboration Expert.

At PGi we have a global sales team and understand the importance of being able to meet with your client throughout the sales cycle. I know also know first hand the importance of getting all the right people in the right place the close the deal. Here’s where we can help.

Our audio conferencing solution GlobalMeet Audio takes traditional teleconferencing to an entirely new level. GlobalMeet Audio enables your participants to join anytime, anywhere and from any device.


Increase Sales Rep Activity &amp; Productivity

Easily invite prospects and clients to meetings
Don’t waste time getting to meetings with our unique quick one click access
Achieve new levels of sales productivity as you will be able host more meetings every week
Never lose productivity, even while you’re on the go with the GlobalMeet Audio mobile app
Schedule, start and run meetings from your Outlook calendar or mobile device – no disruption to business
One-Click Access, it doesn’t matter how you would like to connect
Control meetings using audio controls from your keypad, desktop or mobile
High quality solution

Impress prospects using a superior and high quality audio product

I would also welcome the opportunity to demonstrate how PGi can help your sales team become more productive and would like to book a 60 minute meeting to learn more about your meeting requirements – we have some great ideas we want to share with you!

I will contact you shortly to arrange a convenient time.

Yours sincerely

{!Contact.FirstName},

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}

{!User.Title}
{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
