<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Use this as a first contact with a SUSPECT with an IT title</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Suspects: IT, 1st Contact</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Do your workers use tablets for business?</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName}, 

Have you seen an increased use of tablets in the workplace? If so, you may be interested in this recent study from Forrester on this emerging trend and the impact of adding web conferencing tools to tablets can have on collaboration.  Click here to read the research, Adding Web Conferencing Tools To Tablets Fosters Mobile Collaboration: http://cdn2.hubspot.net/hub/147341/file-17880780-pdf/docs/forrester_tech_adoption_survey.pdf

One stat from Forrester’s research that jumped out at me was that 72% of tablet users report that meeting access – either getting everyone into a meeting or participating in a meeting away from a desktop or laptop – is the main stumbling block to using web conferencing at their companies. In working with over 40,000 customers worldwide and 75% of the Fortune 100™,  PGi has found 3 key challenges common to enterprise organizations:

-iPads, tablets and smartphones integrating into existing technology platforms (BYOD)

-High cost and low usage of video telepresence rooms versus the ease of use of HD video conferencing tools

-Fragmented approach of current audio, web and video conferencing solutions

PGi enables companies to consolidate their entire organization&apos;s audio, web and video conferencing needs making it easier to meet anywhere, anytime and on virtually any device.

I&apos;d like the opportunity to share with you how PGi&apos;s award-winning collaboration solutions can meet your needs. Please let me know your availability for a 15-minute virtual meeting by contacting me at the information below; otherwise I will follow up with you next week.

Sincerely,

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}
{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}

P.S.  If you are not the correct person to speak to about collaboration solutions within your organization, it would be great if you would direct me to the correct individual. Thanks in advance for your help!

AWARDS &amp; ACCOLADES

Best New Product – iMeet 2012 Silver Edison Award
People’s Choice – iMeet 2011 Stevie Award
Most Innovative Tech Company of the Year 2012 Silver Stevie Award
Top 250 Innovators of the Year InformationWeek

‘iMeet has succeeded where many others have failed.’ ZDNet
‘A wonderful convergence of usability, responsiveness and connectivity.’ TechRepublic

© 2013 PGi  3280 Peachtree Road, N.E., Suite 1000 Atlanta, GA 30305 USA
© Premiere Global Services, Ltd.  |  PGi All rights reserved.

If you prefer not to receive emails from PGi sales representatives, you may  unsubscribe: http://experts.pgi.com/email-opt-out</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
