<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Use this as a second contact with a SUSPECT that has a Sales title</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Suspects: Sales 2nd Contact</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Following up - improve your prospect calls</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName},

Did you know that 80% of communication is nonverbal? Holding conference calls to conduct your sales appointments can be a barrier to your success if you can’t read your prospects nonverbal cues. How do you know your prospect is engaged?

As one of PGi’s meetings &amp; collaborations experts, I am keenly aware of the collaboration challenges faced by enterprise organizations, particularly Sales departments. PGi has over 40,000 customers worldwide and works with 75% of the Fortune 100™.

We offer a suite of collaboration solutions to support your unique video, web or audio needs. Whether for your individual department or across the organization – PGi makes it easier to meet anyone, anywhere, anytime, on virtually any device.

For more information on our collaboration solutions, check out the video links below:

-Watch this video testimonial on how Idea Harvest uses iMeet: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NNxwMjzHP2U

-Here is how it works – watch this video using iMeet for Sales: http://youtu.be/Qb2qAela5zA

Our collaboration solutions are unique to experience and very easy to use – but you have to see it to believe it. Please let me know your availability for a 15-minute virtual meeting.

During our virtual meeting, I will show you how PGi helps organizations improve their communication and collaboration. Please feel free to contact me at the information below. Otherwise, I will follow up with you shortly to be sure you received this email.

Sincerely,

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName}
{!User.Title}
{!User.Email}
{!User.Phone}

P.S.  If you are not the correct person to speak to about collaboration solutions within your organization, it would be great if you would direct me to the correct individual. Thanks in advance for your help!

AWARDS &amp;
ACCOLADES

Best New Product – iMeet 2012 Silver Edison Award
People’s Choice – iMeet 2011 Stevie Award
Most Innovative Tech Company of the Year 2012 Silver Stevie Award
Top 250 Innovators of the Year InformationWeek

‘iMeet has succeeded where many others have failed.’ ZDNet
‘A wonderful convergence of usability, responsiveness and connectivity.’ TechRepublic

© 2013 PGi  3280 Peachtree Road, N.E., Suite 1000 Atlanta, GA 30305 USA
© Premiere Global Services, Ltd.  |  PGi All rights reserved.

If you prefer not to receive emails from PGi sales representatives, you may  unsubscribe: http://experts.pgi.com/email-opt-out</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
